Seidenberg, Jacob Additional Arbitration Files 5519
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Elgin, Joliet & Eastern Railway Company: Special Board of Adjustment No. 455 -- Cases 23, 24, 25, 26 and 27 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Hostler Cases: Special Board of Adjustments No. 455 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 455 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Special Board of Adjustment #455: Item No. 28 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- SBA #455: Cases 8,9,10,11,12 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- SBA #459: Great Northern SUNA Award 6-11 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Hostlers: Joilet Division (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Brief of South Buffalo Railway Company: Case No. 4 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- P.L. Board No. 474: Southern -- BLE -- Award No. 8 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- P.L. #458: Award No. 3 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Award No. 14: P.L. Board 474 -- Southern -- BLE (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Award No. 1 - - Public Law Board #458 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Award No. 2 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- SBA #459: Great Northern -- RR & SUNA Award 1-3 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- SBA #459: Great Northern -- SUNA Award 4-5 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Award No. 6: P.L. 474 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Award No. 3: P.L. Board No. 474 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- No. 17: P.L. Board No. 474 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Award No. 2: P.L. Board #474 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- P.L. Board No. 474: Southern -- BLE -- Award No. 9 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Public Law Board 474: Southern -- BLE -- Award 2010 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- P.L. Board No. 474: Southern -- BLE -- Award No. 12 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Award No. 16: P.L. Board No. 474 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Award No. 4; P.L. #458: Award No. 3 (Box 9, Folder 13)